为下一位选手鼓掌。
你准备好了吗？
你敢吗？
我们安排马。他去了。
完成的？
下一个已经在马上。
宝贝，怎么了？
看。
我们要回家吗？
- 爸爸呢？
我们要找到他。来。
你在这。
吃冰淇淋太热了。
- 但是你在温暖的时候吃它们。
如果你把它们清理干净，
他们没有融化。
但你总是这样做。
首先是冰箱里的冰淇淋
然后养肥。这里。
我不喝。
- 一点点，你喜欢。
那是什么？
警卫。
今天早上来了一个人。
法警？
- 是的。
我不得不付给他 28,733.17 欧元……
否则我必须在一个月内
离开我的房子。
你有 28,733.17 欧元吗？
- 你怎么看？
我钱包里有 35 欧元。
你丈夫蒂娜呢？
- 不。
对不起。
蒂娜。
萨维诺？
一切都好吗？
- 打扰一下。
您将赶上下一个班次。
- 好的。
对不起。
你好。
她已收到驱逐通知。
- 驱逐？
我们能做点什么吗？
28,733 欧元不是猫尿。
应该按时支付。
我们一直在做我们能做的。
的确。
你快乐吗？
那是错的吗？
我在 17 岁时得到了第一个吻。
我在读高中。
他很棒。
我爱他。
住口。即使你是最后一个女孩
在地球上，他不会带走你。
我应该马上张开嘴吗？
- 是的。
不，只是在最后。
我的表弟慢慢地打开它。
- 你是什么意思？这不是前门。
我想马上，但不要太多，
因为他还应该做什么？
也许。
别理她
她对此一无所知。
我们去吗？
嘿，咪玛。
再见宝贝。
亲爱的。
真可惜，咪玛。
多么浪费。
好纯洁的妈妈...
- 为我们祷告。
处女座...
纯洁的母亲...
- 为我们祷告。
可爱的妈妈...
敬佩的妈妈...
- 为我们祷告。
你在这里做什么？
她真的很红
是的。
但是天色越来越暗了。
那正确吗？
- 是的。
机关是不是太阴暗了
对于一个八岁的孩子？
两周后她就十岁了。
21号吧？
是的，21号。
器官很漂亮。
她喜欢它。
这是为了纪念圣母。
和...
我卖野兽
然后我就永远离开了。
你介意吗？
- 自然。
我也是。非常。
你不吃吗？
我已经吃了。
教堂里的那个女人是谁，妈妈？
那是...
一个迷失的灵魂，一个可怜的女人。
她住在村外
并且永远不会来这里。
她也参加了牛仔竞技表演。
- 哦耶？
好好洗脚。也在你的脚趾之间。
你总是在那里留下污垢。
晚安。
晚安宝贝。
- 相信，爸爸。
丢弃。明天就不好了。
- 我带它去上班。
她今天在教堂。
去看她。
你觉得她想要什么吗？
- 她有一张去大陆的票。
但她问我是否
可以带到她家。一次。
然后这样做。
她在附近住了这么久，
如果她想要什么，她就会说出来。
等等，亲爱的。
关门。
当归？
- 你怀孕了。
荡妇。你是个荡妇。
- 当归。
我知道这不是你的错。
我原谅你，但我不能再
照顾好你和你的混蛋。
明白了吗，婊子？
快点，出去。
离开。
你在这里。
再见，维多利亚。
我是安洁莉卡
它是什么？她为什么这样看我？
- 问好。
她会和萨维诺的狗交配。
每只小狗15欧元。
但她被抓住了
被一只流浪狗。你明白吗？
当我找到她时，她非常高兴。
我不能再照顾她了。
我得走了。我得走了。
你想保留这个吗？
- 把它放在那个盒子里。
这个？
- 是的。
还有这个。
不要碰猫头鹰。
它是神圣的。
她总是和马在一起。
- 维多利亚？
她很听话。
- 非常。
来。
最后一次。
做得好。
我的宝贝。
贾科米诺。
我可以吃些腰果吗？
腰果到底是什么？
弯曲的坚果？
猴。
学校的老师叫我猴子。
所以我是猴子。
之后大家都叫我猴子。
妈妈，告诉老师...
...坟墓包含许多碎片。
如果我们从后面...
- 孔太窄。
是的，但是有东西...
- 它太紧。
它可以带来很多钱。
- 让我们去那里。
多少钱？
超过 28,733 欧元？
- 多得多。
但是要进去
你一定是个口水。
一个刀片。
- 尼古拉斯。
什么是腰果？
- 腰果。
我喜欢你，因为你说的那些话
像他们那样。给我买一杯。
回家。你受够了。
- 我还得付钱。
你知道我马上就要走了。
我离开了房子和一切。
想我一会儿，
你再也见不到我了。
善待。
请我喝一杯。
最后，然后你去。
- 贾科米诺，尼古拉为我付钱。
尼古拉的屁股，
我们需要谈谈这个。
狗。
狗，那就来吧。
我的小荡妇回来了。
你想要冰淇淋吗？
出色地？
这只狗的名字叫Luciana，
就像我妈妈一样。
她是个婊子，就像所有的母亲一样。
这很伤人。
- 我该怎么办，女士？
你没看到我流血到死吗？
把水放进去。
你没那么聪明吧？
我喜欢“夫人”。
赶快。
还没有乳头？
来，帮帮我。
清理。
你有什么小手。
你有多高？
- 我不知道。
最后一次是三十四英尺。
你有多重？
- 25 磅。
你是个聪明人。
你跑过吗？
你看起来像个洋娃娃
在英式饼干罐上...
他们卖的那些黄油曲奇
在有钱人的超市里。
你喜欢那些饼干吗？
妈妈说你的脚趾必须很好
洗，因为那是污垢会沉淀的地方。
污垢无处不在
你什么也不做。
下次我们去
到一个美丽的地方。
这是美丽而出乎意料的。
当我邀请你去海边时，我没有
期待我的梦想成真。
我一直爱着你
我们必须撒谎也没关系。
亲爱的，我想回到开始的地方，
不用害怕。
女士。
它是什么？
我不想下去。
我害怕空虚。
你说的“害怕空虚”是什么意思？
你没看到虚空中什么都没有吗？
没有什么好害怕的。
来。
就一个人回去吧。
天。
女士。
亲爱的？
它是什么？
发生了什么事吗？一切都顺利吗？
- 很高兴见到你。
而我，你，宝贝。
妈妈会做肉丸吗？
- 你不累吗？
那不重要。你帮我吗？
然后我们准备好了。
爸爸不在家吗？
爸爸，我出生的时候你在吗？
没有心肝宝贝。
我们亲吻了对方
它仍然坚持
放下这份爱
总是冒险
回到你身边
但我不害怕
我是色情之王
没有王冠的国王
但有抽动
会出击的国王
如果你拒绝他
所以表现出胆量然后走开
因为如果你留下
你让事情变得更糟了吗
再爱一次
就像我们没有
放手
这份爱
你去过超蒙特吗？
什么？
我以为你不喜欢山。
那是真实的。
我没有去过Supramonte。
我觉得很可怕。
多么奇怪。
我敢肯定我最近在那里看到了维多利亚。
- 维多利亚？
我以为你在她身后走。
但你当时确实有转变。
- 是的。
不是维多利亚。
- 我发誓我做到了。
很多女孩都没有这样的头发。
真的是维多利亚。
现在你是一个美丽的女人。
抓紧。你知道吗
我们怎么处理一匹瘸腿的马？
不。
- 我们会在他的头上放一颗子弹。
如果他跛脚，那是你的错
我向你开枪。
只是在开玩笑。
我什至没有枪。
蒂娜喜欢你吗？
- 一点。
真正的？
然后她说了什么？
没有什么。
维多利亚？
维多利亚在哪里，妈妈？
她写道，她和马塞拉在一起。
在马塞拉？
真可爱。
她甚至画了一颗心。
她最近去旅行了。
你怎么什么都没说？
来吧，马。
你要对我的小马做什么？
- 你怎么看？
你卖的很好，对吧？
来，拿去。
拿着这个。
该死。
逝者安息，
生者关心。
再见，宝贝。
进来。
快一点。
你到底要去哪里？
我再从你那里得到 200 欧元。
你还是明白的。
- 200 欧元。
穿上衣服。
现在我欠那个混蛋200美元。
他们是我的小马，混蛋。
那是我的房子，混蛋。
然而？
是的，橡子。
- 嘿。
不要那么粗鲁，你。
我不能看你。
我从你那里得到 200 欧元，女孩。
清除？
它是什么？
看看你有没有天使皮肤。
- 我没有。
你不被允许撒谎。
出来。
我自己做。
把那些戒指摘下来。
- 他们对我很好看。我很漂亮。
你今天从奶奶那里得到了吗？
- 是的。
给我买一杯。
你保证过。
你又在坚持？
你从不感到羞耻吗？
谢谢你。
是我的朋友。他在胡闹。
这是个玩笑，对吧？
蒂娜。蒂娜来了。
起初他们不想接吻
然后他们像屁股一样吮吸......
就像他们想吸你一样。
这不就是爱吗？
贾科米诺，给我一杯利口酒。
我女朋友付钱。
她付钱。
- 是的。
贾科米诺不喜欢多说话。
你喜欢其他的东西，
是贾科米诺吗？
但事后他总是要哭，
因为他的妻子。
也许这就是为什么他可以
不爱我。
我们在一起会很好的，不是吗？
贾科米诺已经和他的妻子在一起 16 年了。
我没有反对他的妻子。
她对我有意见吗？
- 她是他的妻子。
我们应该是朋友
因为我们想要一样。
你再也见不到维多利亚了。
为什么我再也见不到她了？
- 我们达成了协议。
你答应过会一直帮助我的。
- 我一直都在帮助你。
但是他们把我赶出了我的房子。
- 我对此无能为力。
维多利亚是我的。
因为我把她给了你。
的确。
你确实把她给了我。
这对每个人来说都是最好的。
你知道的。
它就是这样儿的。
你从来不想要她。
她自己来了。
她亲自拜访了我。
她说你知道
她回来了。
她回来了，
因为她喜欢和我在一起。
警卫。
你会为另一个付钱吗？
- 是的。
她说她会再付一笔。
你的票是什么时候买的？
什么时候？
仔细听我说。
听。
离开。
去一个美丽的地方
别处...
一个不错的地方。
你知道该做什么。
我说了什么？
我必须卖掉这些野兽。
- 是的，全部卖掉。
赚点钱
旅行前。
我和 Umberto 将永远帮助你。
总是。
你能看出我想要给你最好的吗？
是的。
你关心我。
- 是的。
我送你回家好吗？
- 我没有房子了。
他们把我赶出去了。
- 天气。
我欠他们 28,733 欧元。
- 我知道。
我知道。
我不想离开。
你要离开这里做什么？什么？
- 我走了。真正的。
我离开。
新生活。
新生活吧？
我们为新生活干杯。
玛丽...
让这几周很快过去。
让一切回到从前的样子。
加油，妈妈在看着你。
再见，蒂娜。
- 你好。
好热啊。
安吉丽卡，你在睡觉吗？
你会关注这样的事情吗？
来吧，我们在钓鱼。
向安吉莉卡展示它是如何完成的。
来吧，已经很晚了。赶快。
来吧，快一点。
来吧。请快点。
你现在在这里工作吗？
- 我在 Savino 工作了几天。
我不想卖掉我的小马。
你说你要走了。
你怎么这么不客气？
你答应永远善良。
- 我很不错。
也许我有一个解决方案
在房子前面。
听。
当她晚上移动时，我能感觉到。
九年来我知道每一次咳嗽，
我女儿的流感或流汗。
她知道我一直在她身边。
如果她转身，我会在那里。
她需要那个。
这治愈了她。
我祈求你...
为什么一定要给她治病？
她病了吗？
你怕她和我一样。
蒂娜，你知道，如果她想要那样，她...
- 现在一切都变了。
你明白？我从来没有过她
必须要给她。
绝不。
这是你的错。
你不能把她关在家里。
你为什么不说
她为萨维诺工作？
你现在高兴了？
然后说你开心。
那我回来陪你睡觉。
你一直无法承受
我们一起拥有的东西。
那不是真的。我爱维多利亚。
你想要一个长得像你的男孩。
用你丑陋的耳朵和弯曲的鼻子。
你父亲说什么了？
“她不是你的。”
我从没有说过。
我爱维多利亚。
你想惩罚我。
你想要那个。
你为什么让我远离？
你像狗一样拴着我。
当你们互相拥抱
并一起交谈。
她是不是我的女儿？
孩子因此而受苦。我认为
她一定知道她妈妈是谁。
你夺走了我的心
并给了她。
这不是真的，亲爱的。
我们必须给她一些东西。
一切。
我们有 2000 欧元
和维多利亚的钱。
你可以卖东西。
- 不。
为什么不？
我们不再为维多利亚买单了。
他不会死在地上吗？
- 看起来像这样吗？帮我。
来。
你看见了吗？
小的都是雄性。
这是一个女性。
她真的肿了。
当她产卵时，她会改变。
她从上面变黑
肚皮变成银色。
晚上雌性来了，
肿了，出水了……
他们去海里游泳
然后几天...
到美国附近的广阔海域。
- 大西洋。
你是谁？
- 早上好。我钓到了一条鳗鱼。
多么伟大。谁说这是允许的？
- 当归。我给了她10欧元。
你是谁的女儿？
- 她是翁贝托和蒂娜的女儿。
那正确吗？
你要对 Piras 的女儿做什么？
- 来吧，回家吧。
她看起来像你。
听着，鳗鱼的事我很抱歉。
当归说他们出生
在海洋中...
然后他们回来
到母亲从哪里来。
真的吗？
- 是的。
这一个也会消失并死去吗？
我认同。她肿了。
她为什么要跑这么远？
她为什么不留在男孩身边？
她不想看吗？
都说人是复杂的，
但有时这也适用于自然。
我知道它即将结束。
但你不能就这样离开我。
我只能想到我们的吻，
但我现在得走了。对不起。
票，钱。
去吧。
在这里，还有一张票。
你不给我钱吗？
告诉维多利亚你想收买我。
告诉她。
告诉她她想收买我。
你说那是我们所有的钱？
我们一收到就给她寄更多，
只要她没有看到维多利亚。
她只想要200欧元。
- 但是你说...
没什么好说的。
她不一样。
让我们离开这里。
然后我们离开。
我们离开。
- 那你想去哪里？
她总能证明
她是母亲。
来。抱着我。
你必须在里面呼吸。
不是用鼻子，而是在里面。你明白吗？
从内部呼吸。
你有没有像我说的那样呼吸？
- 是的，在里面。
做得好。
如果空气较少，请不要害怕。
最美好的东西往往都快死了。
- 你不能唤醒死者。
为什么不？也许他们发现
一个小公司很好。
他们只是骨头。
你不必害怕。
一切都在循环
回到过去的样子。
来。
你在那里看到了吗？
回到那里。
那是找到那张图片的地方
那个胖女人。
它是如此之小，
但它值得很多钱。
但你是我的亲生母亲，对吧？
或多或少。
你离开我了吗
因为我又丑又傻？
是的。
但它会变得更好。
我可以问你一些事情吗？
那么容易的事。
接吻的时候嘴巴怎么办？
我不知道我为什么让你失望
已经离开了。
谁知道。
多年后我回到了村子。
我怀孕了。
我参加母亲的葬礼迟到了。
蒂娜刚到
我生的时候。
没有她，我就活不下去。
她帮助我把你带到了这个世界。
你之前是...
你是个东西。
你非常非常小...
和肮脏的。
每个人都说我什么都做不好
但是蒂娜一路打扫你。
诸如此类的一切。
这很干净
她真的很想要你。
你可以做很多事情。她撒谎了。
- 不。
你不应该这么说。
你不能那样谈论蒂娜。
而你也撒谎。你说她很开心
你是来看我的，但你不是。
她是个好人。
当归。
给我喝点东西。
不，这对你不利。
来吧。
只有这个。好的？
足够的。停止。
你告诉她了吗？
你告诉过我。
你不明白。
她不像以前那样看着我。
晚上我爱她
离我这么近。
我闻到了她的小脚丫。
她不会有事。
现在我不能再拥抱她了。
为什么？
你为什么要这样对我？
冷静下来。
安静的。
为什么？
- 安静的。
她可能比我们两个更好。
为什么？
她自己说的。
我恨你。
你听到我了吗？
你带钱吗？
今天是星期几？
什么？
- 今天是星期几？
20 日。
哦，是的，确实是20号。
慢慢地。
看着她。
酒驳船。
一个可怜的妓女。
不，维多利亚。
- 让她走。
把那个孩子带走。
- 不要碰她。
保持冷静。停止。离开。
维多利亚，你伤到自己了吗？
- 你疯了。不安。
该死。
佛朗哥。
回家。
跟我来。
来。
- 我不和你一起去。
你为什么把她带到这里来？
- 你买了我。
你不在乎我或我想要什么。
你恨我，因为我不像你。
你不关心我。
我不恨你。我...
我真的很爱你。
- 不要碰我。
回家。
- 也不要碰她。
说谎者。
- 你是我的全部。跟我来。
来。
离开。
他伤害你了吗？
发誓。
- 我发誓。
你的膝盖？
他不坏。
他很兴奋，
因为他真的很想要我。
他是...
我的未婚妻。
你把他送走了。
我现在在这里。
回家吧，妈妈。
佛朗哥。
没那么近。我很臭。
对不起，如果你在我身边
做了一些愚蠢的事情。
你必须吃早餐和东西。
我家里没有太多东西
因为我几乎从不吃早餐。
等一等。
这里。
我有这个。
它尝起来像橘子。很好。
你看，它在嗡嗡作响。
来吧，坐在那里。
你不想要这个吗？
这对你有好处。
够了。谢谢你。
不喜欢豆子？
- 是的，非常。谢谢你。
我也是。
请您用餐。
- 你也是。
什么肚子。你的小狗什么时候来？
- 卢西亚娜，出去。
卢西亚娜。卢西亚尼娜。
- 出去。
看，卢西亚娜。
来玩吧，卢西亚娜。
看棍子。来。
看，卢西亚娜。
看。
卢西亚尼娜，来玩吧。
我可以打电话给妈妈吗？
是的当然。
在这儿等着。
出去。
这里。
妈妈？
- 维多利亚，你吃了吗？
是的，我已经吃过。
我可以叫你妈妈吗？
反正宝贝。
你看过爱恋的折磨吗？
不，我们可以一起看
你什么时候回来。
一切都准备好了。
你的朋友也来了。
没人来。
是的。他们都来了。
维多利亚...
我必须挂断电话。天。
- 亲爱的。
维多利亚在哪里？
- 她会在那里。
她今天十岁吗？
- 是的，你不知道吗？
较高一些。
我不认为她会来。
我把小马绑起来
按照你的要求。
我们去。
我们去哪？
- 嘴巴紧闭。
一切都顺利吗？
- 我说闭嘴。
我头疼。
这儿这儿。
这里是。
什么东西在那里？
我不知道。
他们说，宝藏。
我们必须进去吗？
你进去。
我过不去太小。
我教了你所有你需要知道的。
不要害怕空虚。
屏住呼吸。吸入。
然后你推开并再次出来。
去吧。
有人去过吗？
- 不。
来吧。
出色地？
它是什么？
你期待什么？
进去。
我就是这样。
你不应该对我有任何期望。
下雨的时候，我就像大地。
离得越近，沉得越深。
我需要钱。
我一无所有或没有人。清除？
我不能失去房子。
你没有把小马卖给我。
现在怎么办？
这是你的错。你明白吗？
离开。离开。
去。
蒂娜是对的。
我从没想过你。绝不。你可以
没有什么。你只会发牢骚。哭。
你丑陋、愚蠢和无用。
离开。
你很恶心，我诅咒你。
你们都在撒谎。
离开。
我对你没用。
没用的孩子。
你甚至不能爬进洞里。
我没有你的钱。
- 让我走。
你让我感到恶心，
你的和你他妈的钱。
停下来。
你在做什么？
不，不...
- 你不付钱，所以现在他们是我的了。
明白了吗？它们是我的。
- 他们来自维多利亚。远离他们。
明白了吗？远离他们。
- 发布。
她爱他们。
足够的。
发生了什么？
维多利亚。
维多利亚在哪里？她在哪？
发生了什么？她在哪？
我问她想不想进去
爬行。在墓地。
打扰一下。
对不起。你见过女孩吗？
一个红头发的女孩。
我的女儿有危险。
- 我不懂你。对不起。
你没有遗漏什么吗？
我爬进了最深的洞。
独自的。
做得好。
你总是那么勇敢。
恭喜。
你已经长这么大了。
我的宝贝。
我们在这儿。
这很伤人。
警卫。
你爬进去了吗？
- 是的。
我也爬了出来。
什么都没有。
过来。
是水。
它刺痛。
- 是水。
我们走吧。
向前。
A round of applause for the next contestant.
Are you ready?
Do you dare?
We arrange the horse. There he goes.
Finished?
The next one is already on the horse.
Baby, what's up?
Look.
Are we going home?
- What about daddy?
We're going to find him. come.
There you are.
It's too hot to get ice cream.
- But you eat them when it's warm.
If you had cleaned them up,
they hadn't melted.
But you always do.
First the ice cream in the freezer
and then fatten. Here.
I do not drink.
- A little, you like it.
What is that?
Guard.
This morning a guy came by.
A bailiff?
- Yes.
I had to pay him 28,733.17 euros...
otherwise i have to in a month
out of my house.
Do you have 28,733.17 euros?
- What do you think?
I have 35 euros in my wallet.
And your husband, Tina?
- No.
Sorry.
Tina.
Savino?
Everthing okay?
- Excuse me.
You will catch up on the next shift.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Hello.
She has been given an eviction notice.
- An eviction?
Can we do something?
28,733 euros is not cat pee.
It should have been paid on time.
We've always done what we could.
Indeed.
Are you happy?
Is that wrong?
I got my first kiss when I was 17.
I was in high school.
He is great.
I love him.
Shut up. Even if you were the last girl
on earth, he wouldn't take you.
Should I open my mouth right away?
- Yes.
No, only at the end.
My cousin opens it slowly.
- How do you mean? It's not a front door.
I think right away, but not too much,
because what else should he do?
Perhaps.
Don't mind her
she knows nothing about it.
Shall we go?
Hey, Mimma.
Bye, baby.
sweetie.
What a shame, Mimma.
What a waste.
Very chaste mother...
- Pray for us.
Virgin Mother...
Immaculate Mother...
- Pray for us.
Lovely Mother...
Admirable Mother...
- Pray for us.
What are you doing here?
She's really redheaded.
Yes.
But it's getting darker.
Is that right?
- Yes.
Isn't the organ too gloomy
for an eight year old?
She will be ten in two weeks.
The 21st, right?
Yes, the 21st.
The organ is beautiful.
She loves it.
It is in honor of the Virgin.
And...
I sell the beasts
and then I'll be gone for good.
Do you mind?
- Naturally.
Me too. Very.
Don't you eat?
I already ate.
Who was that woman in the church, Mama?
That was...
a lost soul, a poor woman.
She lives outside the village
and never comes here.
She was also at the rodeo.
- Oh yeah?
Wash your feet well. Also between your toes.
You always leave dirt in there.
Good night.
Good night, baby.
- Trust, Dad.
Throw away. It won't be good tomorrow.
- I take it to work.
She was at church today.
To see her.
Do you think she wants something?
- She has a ticket for the mainland.
But she asked if I
could bring to her home. For once.
Then do that.
She's lived close by for so long,
if she had wanted something, she would have said it.
Wait, honey.
Close the door.
Angelica?
- You are pregnant.
Slut. You're a slut.
- Angelica.
I know it's not your fault.
I forgive you but I can't anymore
take care of you and your bastards.
Got it, bitch?
Hurry up, get out.
Away.
You are here.
Bye, Victoria.
I'm Angelica.
What is it? Why is she looking at me like that?
- Say hello.
She would mate with Savino's dog.
15 euros per puppy.
But she gets caught
by a stray dog. Do you understand?
She was so happy when I found her.
I can't take care of her anymore.
I have to leave. I have to leave.
Do you want to keep this?
- Put it in that box.
This?
- Yes.
And this one too.
Don't touch the owl.
It is holy.
She is always with the horses.
- Victoria?
She is obedient.
- Very.
come.
The last time.
Well done.
My baby.
Giacomino.
Can I have some cashew nuts?
What are cashews anyway?
Bent nuts?
Monkey.
The teacher at school called me monkey.
So I was the monkey.
After that everyone called me monkey.
Mama, tell the teacher...
...the grave contains many pieces.
If we go through the back...
- The hole is too narrow.
Yes, but there's stuff...
- It's too tight.
It can bring in a lot of money.
- Let's go there.
How much money?
More than 28,733 euros?
- Much more.
But to get in
you must be a spit.
A blade.
- Nicholas.
What are cashew nuts?
- Cashew nuts.
I like you because you say the things
as they are. Buy me a drink.
Go home. You've had enough.
- I still have to pay.
You know I'm leaving soon.
I leave the house and everything behind.
Think of me for a moment,
you will never see me again.
Be kind.
Treat me to a drink.
The last and then you go.
- Giacomino, Nicola pays for me.
Nicola's ass,
we need to talk about that.
Dog.
Dog, come then.
My little slut is back.
Do you want icecream?
Well?
The dog's name is Luciana,
just like my mother.
She was a bitch, like all mothers.
It hurts so much.
- What should I do, ma'am?
Can't you see I'm bleeding to death.
Put water in it.
You're not that bright, are you?
I like 'ma'am'.
Hurry up.
Don't have tits yet?
Come on, help me.
Clean it up.
What small hands you have.
How tall are you?
- I do not know.
The last time thirty-four feet.
And how much do you weigh?
- 25 pounds.
You are a wit.
Do you ever run?
You look like such a doll
on an English biscuit tin...
Those butter cookies they sell
in supermarkets for rich people.
Do you like those cookies?
Mama says you have to be good between your toes
wash, because that's where the dirt will settle.
Dirt gets everywhere
and you do nothing about it.
Next time we go
to a beautiful place.
It was beautiful and unexpected.
When I invited you to the sea, I didn't
expect my dream to come true.
I have always loved you
and it doesn't matter that we have to lie.
Darling, I want to go back to where it started,
without being afraid.
Madam.
What is it?
I don't want to go down.
I'm afraid of the void.
What do you mean by 'afraid of the void'?
Can't you see there's nothing in the void?
There is nothing to be afraid of.
come.
Just go back alone.
Day.
Madam.
Darling?
What is it?
Did something happen? Is everything all right?
- I'm so glad to see you.
And me you, baby.
Will mommy make meatballs?
- Are not you tired?
That does not matter. Do you help me?
Then we're ready.
Is daddy not at home?
Daddy, were you there when I was born?
No darling.
We kissed each other
And it still sticks
Hands off this love
It's always adventure
to return to you
But I'm not afraid
I am the king of porn
A king without a crown
but with tics
A king who will strike
if you reject him
So show guts and go away
'Cause if you stay
do you make it worse
Make love one more time
would be like we didn't
hands off
of this love
Have you been to Supramonte?
What?
I thought you didn't like mountains.
That is true.
I have not been to Supramonte.
I find it scary.
How strange.
I'm sure I saw Vittoria there recently.
- Victoria?
I thought you were walking behind her.
But you actually had a shift back then.
- Yes.
It wasn't Victoria.
- I'd swear I did.
So many girls don't have hair like that.
It really was Victoria.
Now you are a beautiful woman.
Hold tight. Do you know
what do we do with a lame horse?
No.
- We'll put a bullet in his head.
If he gets lame, it's your fault
and I shoot you.
Just kidding.
I don't even have a gun.
Does Tina like you here?
- A little.
For real?
Then what did she say?
Nothing.
Victoria?
Where's Vittoria, Mom?
She wrote that she is with Marcella.
At Marcella?
How cute.
She even drew a heart.
She recently went on a trip.
Why didn't you say anything?
Come on, horse.
What are you going to do with my ponies?
- What do you think?
You sold them well, right?
Here, take it.
Take this.
damn.
The dead rest,
the living are concerned.
Bye, honey.
Get in.
Come on, hurry up.
Where the hell are you going?
I get another 200 euros from you.
You still get that.
- 200 euros.
Get the clothes on.
Now I owe that jerk $200.
They're my ponies, jerk.
And that's my house, jerk.
However?
Yes, acorn.
- Hey.
Not so rude, you.
I can't look at you.
I get 200 euros from you, girl.
Clear?
What is it?
Let's see if you have angel skin.
- I do not have.
You are not allowed to lie.
Come out.
I do it myself.
Take those rings off.
- They look good on me. I am beautiful.
Did you get them from grandma today?
- Yes.
Buy me a drink.
You promised.
Are you insisting again?
Are you never ashamed?
Thank you.
It's my friend. He's fooling around.
It's a joke, right?
Tina. Tina is here.
At first they don't want to kiss
and then they suck as hard as an ass...
like they want to suck you up.
That's love isn't it?
Giacomino, give me a liqueur.
My girlfriend pays.
She pays.
- Yes.
Giacomino doesn't like to talk much.
you like other things,
is it Giacomino?
But he always has to cry afterwards,
because of his wife.
Maybe that's why he can
don't love me.
We'd be fine together, wouldn't we?
Giacomino has been with his wife for 16 years.
I have nothing against his wife.
Does she have something against me?
- She's his wife.
We should be friends
because we want the same.
You can't see Vittoria anymore.
Why can't I see her anymore?
- We had an agreement.
You promised you would always help me.
- I've always helped you.
But they kicked me out of my house.
- There's nothing I can do about that.
Victoria is mine.
Because I gave her to you.
Indeed.
You did indeed give her to me.
That was best for everyone.
You know that.
That's the way it is.
You never wanted her.
She came herself.
She visited me herself.
She said you knew
and she came back.
she has come back,
because she likes to be with me.
Guard.
Will you pay for another one?
- Yes.
She said she will pay another one.
For when is your ticket?
When?
Listen to me carefully.
Listen.
Go away.
Go to a beautiful place
elsewhere...
a nice place.
You know what to do.
What did I say?
I have to sell the beasts.
- Yes, sell them all.
Make some money
before the trip.
Me and Umberto will always help you.
Always.
Can you see that I want the best for you?
Yes.
You care about me.
- Yes.
Shall I take you home?
- I don't have a house anymore.
They kicked me out.
- Weather.
I owe them 28,733 euros.
- I know that.
I know.
I don't want to leave.
What are you leaving here? What?
- I'm leaving. For real.
I leave.
A new life.
A new life right?
We toast to a new life.
Mary...
make these weeks pass quickly.
Get everything back to the way it used to be.
Go on, Mama's watching you.
Bye, Tina.
- Hello.
It's so hot.
Angelica, are you sleeping?
Do you keep an eye on things like that?
Come on, we're fishing.
Show Angelica how it's done.
Come on, it's already late. Hurry up.
Come on, a little faster.
Come on. Hurry up, please.
Do you work here now?
- I work for Savino for a few days.
I don't want to sell my ponies.
You said you were leaving.
Why are you being so unkind?
You promised to always be nice.
- I am nice.
Maybe I have a solution
in front of the house.
Listen.
When she moves at night, I can feel it.
For nine years I've known every cough,
my daughter's flu or drop of sweat.
She knows I'm always there for her.
If she turns around, I'll be there.
She needs that.
That heals her.
I beg you...
Why do you have to heal her?
Is she sick?
You're afraid she's just like me.
Tina, you know that if she wants that, she...
- Now everything has changed.
You understand? I never had her
have to take to her.
Never.
It is your fault.
You can't lock her up in the house.
Why didn't you say
that she works for Savino?
Are you happy now?
Then say you're happy.
Then I'll come back to bed with you.
You've never been able to bear
what we have together.
That is not true. I love Victoria.
You wanted a boy who looked like you.
With your ugly ears and crooked nose.
What did your father say?
"She's not yours."
I never said that.
I love Victoria.
You wanted to punish me.
You wanted that.
Why are you keeping me away?
You keep me on a leash like a dog.
While you hug each other
and talk together.
Is she my daughter or not?
The child suffers from this. I think
she must know who her mother is.
you snatched my heart
and given it to her.
That's not true, dear.
We have to give her something.
Everything.
We have 2000 euros
and the money for Vittoria.
You can sell something.
- No.
Why not?
We're not paying for Vittoria anymore.
Won't he die on the ground?
- Does it look like this? Help me.
come.
Did you see that?
The little ones are males.
This is a female.
She's really swollen.
When she spawns, she changes.
She turns black from above
and the belly turns silver.
At night the females come,
that are swollen, out of the water...
they go to the sea and swim
then for days...
to the vast sea off America.
- The Atlantic Ocean.
Who are you?
- Good morning. I caught an eel.
How great. And who said that was allowed?
- Angelica. I gave her 10 euros.
Who are you a daughter of?
- She is the daughter of Umberto and Tina.
Is that right?
What are you doing with Piras' daughter?
- Come on, go home.
She looks like you.
Listen, I'm sorry about the eel.
Angelica said they are born
in the ocean...
and then they return
to where the mother comes from.
Is that true?
- Yes.
Will this one also go away and die?
I think so. She is swollen.
Why does she have to go so far away?
Why doesn't she stay with the boy?
Doesn't she want to see it?
It is said that man is complicated,
but sometimes that also applies to nature.
I knew it was coming to an end.
But you can't leave me like this.
I can only think of our kisses,
but I have to go now. Forgive me.
The ticket, the money.
Just go.
Here, there is also a ticket.
Won't you pay me?
Tell Vittoria you want to buy me off.
Tell her.
Tell her she wants to buy me off.
Did you say that's all our money?
That we'll send her more as soon as we get it,
as long as she doesn't see Vittoria.
She only wanted 200 euros.
- But did you say...
There's nothing to say.
She's different.
Let's get out of here.
Then we leave.
We leave.
- Where do you want to go then?
She can always prove
that she is the mother.
come. Hold me.
You have to breathe inside.
Not with your nose, but inside. Do you understand?
Breathe from within.
Did you breathe like I said?
- Yes, inside.
Well done.
Do not be afraid if there is less air.
The most beautiful things are often almost dead.
- You must not wake the dead.
Why not? Maybe they find
a little company is nice.
They're just bones.
You do not have to be scared.
Everything goes in circles
and go back to how it used to be.
come.
Do you see that there?
Back there.
That's where that image was found
of that fat woman.
it's so small,
but it is worth a lot of money.
But you're my real mother, right?
More or less.
did you leave me
because I was ugly and stupid?
Yes.
But it gets better.
May I ask you something?
Something easy then.
What do you do with your mouth when you kiss?
I don't know why I let you down
have left.
Who knows.
I came back to the village after years.
I was pregnant.
I was late to my mother's funeral.
Tina just arrived
when I was giving birth.
I wouldn't have survived without her.
She helped me bring you into the world.
You were...
You were something.
You were very, very small...
and dirty.
Everyone says I can't do anything right
but Tina cleaned you all the way.
All that sort of thing.
It was clear
that she really wanted you.
You can do a lot. She lies.
- No.
You shouldn't say that.
You can't talk about Tina like that.
And you lie too. You said she was happy
that you came to see me, but you're not.
She's a good person.
Angelica.
Give me something to drink.
No, that's not good for you.
Come on.
Only this. Okay?
Enough. Stop.
Did you tell her?
You told me.
You do not understand.
She doesn't look at me like she used to.
I loved her at night
so close to me.
I smelled her little feet.
Nothing would happen to her.
Now I can't hug her anymore.
Why?
Why did you do this to me?
Calm down.
Quiet.
Why?
- Quiet.
She could be better than the two of us.
Why?
She said it herself.
I hate you.
Did you hear me?
Are you bringing the money?
What day is today?
What?
- What day is today?
The 20th.
Oh yes, indeed, the 20th.
Slowly.
Look at her.
A booze barge.
A poor whore.
No, Victoria.
- Let her go.
Get that kid away.
- Don't touch her.
Stay calm. Stop. Go away.
Vittoria, did you hurt yourself?
- You're crazy. Disturbed.
damn.
Franco.
Come home.
Come with me.
come.
- I'm not going with you.
Why did you bring her here?
- You bought me.
You don't care about me or what I want.
You hate me because I'm not like you.
You don't care about me.
I don't hate you. I...
I love you so much.
- Don't touch me.
Come home.
- Don't touch her either.
liar.
- You're everything to me. Come with me.
come.
Go away.
Did he hurt you?
Swear it.
- I swear.
your knees?
He's not bad.
he was excited,
because he really wanted me.
He is...
my fiancee.
And you sent him away.
I'm here now.
Come home, Mom.
Franco.
Not so close. I stink.
Sorry if you by me
did something stupid.
You have to have breakfast and stuff.
I don't have much in the house
because I hardly ever have breakfast.
Wait a second.
Here.
I have this.
It tastes like orange. It is well.
Look, it's buzzing.
Come on, sit there.
Don't you want this?
It is good for you.
That's enough. Thank you.
Don't like beans?
- Yes, very much. Thank you.
Me too.
Enjoy your meal.
- You too.
What a belly. When are your puppies coming?
- Luciana, get out.
Luciana. Lucianina.
- Get out.
Look, Luciana.
Come play, Luciana.
Look at the stick. come.
Look, Luciana.
Look.
Lucianina, come and play.
Can I call mom?
Yes of course.
Wait here.
Get out.
Here.
Mom?
- Vittoria, have you eaten?
Yes, I have eaten.
Can I call you mommy?
Baby anyway.
Have you watched Tormento d'Amore?
No, we can watch it together
when you return.
Everything is ready here.
Your friends are coming too.
Nobody comes.
Yes. They all come.
Victoria...
I have to hang up. Day.
- Darling.
Where is Vittoria?
- She'll be right there.
Will she be ten today?
- Yeah, didn't you know that?
Slightly higher.
I don't think she's coming.
I tied up the ponies
as you requested.
We go.
Where are we going?
- Mouth closed.
Is everything OK?
- I said shut up.
I have a headache.
Here, here.
Here it is.
What's there?
I do not know.
A treasure, they say.
Do we have to go in there?
You go in.
I can't get through. Too small.
I taught you everything you need to know.
Don't be afraid of the void.
Hold your breath. Breathe in.
Then you push off and come out again.
Just go.
Has anyone ever been in it?
- No.
Come on.
Well?
What is it?
What did you expect?
Go in.
That's how I am.
You shouldn't have expected anything from me.
I am like the earth when it rains.
The closer you get, the deeper you sink.
I need money.
I have nothing or nobody. Clear?
I can't lose the house.
You didn't sell me the ponies.
And what now?
It is your fault. Do you understand?
Go away. Go away.
go.
Tina is right.
I never wanted you. Never. You can
nothing. You just whine. Cry.
You're ugly, stupid and useless.
Go away.
You are disgusting and I curse you.
You all lie.
Go away.
I have no use for you.
Worthless child.
You can't even crawl into a hole.
I don't have your money.
- Let me go.
You make me sick,
yours and your fucking money.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
No no...
- You don't pay, so now they're mine.
Understood? They're mine.
- They're from Vittoria. Stay away from them.
Understood? Stay away from them.
- Release.
She loves them.
Enough.
What happened?
Victoria.
Where is Vittoria? Where is she?
What happened? Where is she?
I asked if she wanted to go in the hole
crawl. In the necropolis.
Excuse me.
Sorry. Have you seen a girl?
A girl with red hair.
My daughter is in danger.
- I do not understand you. Sorry.
Are you not missing anything?
I crawled into the deepest hole.
Alone.
Well done.
You are always so brave.
Congratulations.
You've grown so big.
My darling.
We are here.
It hurts so much.
Guard.
Did you crawl in?
- Yes.
I climbed out too.
There was nothing.
Come here.
It's water.
It stings.
- It's water.
Let's go.
forward.